[Melody of Golden Age]
[Episode 18]
Grand Commander Shen successfully sought justice
for Jinxiu Workshop.
The real culprit has been brought to justice.
It's truly satisfying.
The wronged have been cleared.
This is really wonderful.
The lady of the Shen's Mansion
will be me from now on.
What are you still doing here?
Terrible news!
The Grand Commander insists on reopening the old case.
It has displeased the Grand Empress Dowager.
The entire Shen family is to be executed today.
Shen Du didn't
defy the Grand Empress Dowager.
Xing,
weren't you eager
to know the truth?
Yet now you feel sympathy
for Shen Du.
I don't.
This isn't fair.
There's no such thing as fairness.
Consider me, with my vast knowledge,
yet because of my humble origins,
I can't take the imperial examinations.
The truth
or ensuring Shen Du's safety,
you can only choose one.
I won't choose.
I can't choose.
Get out of here now.
Madam, please save the Grand Commander quickly.
Think of something.
Xing.
Hurry up and choose one.
This place will be all mine from now on.
Madam.
We're all going to be beheaded today.
Don't you want to know the truth?
What are you standing there for?
I won't need
to compete with you anymore.
Madam.
Shen Du.
Knock...
What on earth are you talking about?
Out...
A...
Bull.
What do you mean by "Knock Out A Bull"?
Madam, you're finally awake.
The Grand Commander wishes to discuss something with you.
He has been waiting in the study for quite some time.
Xiaohe,
what time is it now?
Madam, you've been asleep
until the hour of 6 pm.
The sun is about to set.
Could it be that
something is really about to happen?
Here.
I heard you wanted to see me.
[Case File of Jinxiu Workshop]
[12 corpses of Ximing Temple]
Yes.
Did something happen?
These
are the case files for the Jinxiu Workshop incident.
[Case File of Jinxiu Workshop]
I've organized them.
It'll be easier to review later.
What do you mean?
The Grand Empress Dowager has agreed
to reopen the case.
Really?
Do you think I'm
joking with you?
Then you made me...
Worry for nothing.
I thought you would...
Were you worried I'd look out for myself only
and close the case hastily?
Or were you concerned I'd report this matter
and incur the Grand Empress Dowager's displeasure?
Is there a difference between the two?
There is.
Which one were you?
Why do I have to make a choice
after waking up?
I won't choose.
So?
What do you think?
What... what can I think?
I think you're quite upright.
This is exactly what someone
in an important position should do.
Besides this,
is there anything else you want to say?
Say what?
Did I say something wrong again?
No.
It's baffling.
I heard that the Grand Commander at the court
engaged in a fierce debate with the scholars,
showing no fear.
With a passionate and inspiring
speech,
he convinced the Grand Empress Dowager
to agree to reopen the Jinxiu Workshop case.
I suppose
you must have been
behind the scenes, offering advice and strategies.
Your contribution is significant, isn't it?
I don't have any merit.
Instead, I fell victim to Pan Chi's drug
and ended up knocking myself out.
After I woke up,
I heard this news.
Has investigating this case
made you stupid?
It's such a pity.
I've only heard about it,
but haven't been able to witness
the Grand Commander's impressive demeanor.
Him?
He actually spends all day
showing off his authority to me.
You don't know how lucky you are.
The Grand Commander holds an important position,
and has a formidable reputation.
Most importantly, he's good-looking too.
He has a cold expression on his face all day,
it's so unattractive.
Jing Lin.
Yes, Grand Commander.
Am I
unattractive?
Miss Yun Que.
I have something to tell you.
I advise you not to
provoke the Grand Commander right now.
Mind your own business.
Haven't you considered why
the Grand Commander is called...
White Ghost?
I'm different from outsiders.
Just now, the Grand Commander
even changed his expression.
If you still persist,
in case he gets angry,
he might twist your head off.
It's not impossible.
Who are you trying to scare?
If you don't believe me,
go ahead and try.
I'm just curious
about the Jinxiu Workshop case.
Brother Jing Lin,
you often
work on cases with the Grand Commander.
Ji Fangming has already been interrogated,
but regarding the Jinxiu Workshop incident,
who was the original instigator
back then?
You must know some inside information, right?
I...
I don't know.
You definitely know.
Tell me about it.
Then let me ask you,
what kind of relationship does your family have
with Kong Xianrong from Jinxiu Workshop
that makes you work so hard
to reverse the verdict for his case?
Even if I tell you, you won't understand.
If you don't explain clearly,
how can others understand?
What do you mean?
Your family had frequent dealings
with Jinxiu Workshop back then,
yet was never affected.
Why is that?
Are you interrogating me now?
Could it be
you suspect my family?
I...
[Princess Ying's Mansion]
Have you heard?
Hundreds of moths
swarmed into the Princess Ying's Mansion.
It's terrifying.
I heard
they flew over
from Jinxiu Workshop.
They say it's the souls of those who died unjustly,
crying out
and demanding justice.
Could it be that the Princess Ying is
the mastermind behind
the Jinxiu Workshop massacre?
Back then, she was
at odds with Princess Runing,
wasn't she?
Aunt,
regarding the Jinxiu Workshop case,
Mother Empress has agreed to reopen the investigation.
The injustice you've carried for years
can finally be redressed.
The old case can be overturned,
but those who died unjustly
can never be brought back.
Aunt, you still harbor hatred in your heart?
The fact that I can open the door to see you today
means that I have put
the past behind me.
The dead are gone,
and the living
must continue to live well.
Now everyone outside is saying
that the unjust case of Jinxiu Workshop back then
was my doing.
That I caused the death of Aunt's prince consort.
Don't you have anything
you want to ask me?
So?
I didn't do it.
If that's the case,
why is your heart troubled again?
That invisible force
has appeared again.
It's targeting the royal family,
trying to throw us
into chaos.
I'm not the first one,
and you won't be the last.
Knowing there's nothing to be done,
it's better to accept it as fate.
I refuse to accept that fate.
Be it the wrongful case of Jinxiu Workshop,
or the unsolved case of Chen Huo'e,
the Imperial Security Bureau,
the Imperial Investigation Department,
the Court of Judicial Review, the Ministry of Justice,
they're all trying to solve these cases.
We must bring
the truth to light.
The mortal world is full of turmoil.
I only seek clarity in my own heart.
Don't tell me
you want to stay in this Mingsheng Temple
for the rest of your life, Aunt?
The affairs of the world
are nothing but trifles.
Here,
at least, I can find some peace and quiet.
Forget it.
I brought this upon myself.
You're still the same as before.
I can't stand this air of superiority.
You despise my frivolous nature.
I heard that when Prince Xian came,
you once divined for him.
Today,
could you draw a fortune stick for me?
I have been practicing here
for just a few years.
My spiritual attainment is not profound.
When it comes to interpreting fortunes,
I'm not very adept either.
If there's nothing else,
you should head back early.
This is clearly a polite way of asking me to leave.
I know my place.
Our meeting is already a blessing.
Why worry unnecessarily?
Your Highness.
Shen Du?
Your Highness visits Mingsheng Temple at night.
Are you concerned about Chen Huo'e
and the matters of Jinxiu Workshop?
What?
Don't tell me even you suspect me.
Do you want to question me?
Your Highness misunderstands.
I have a plan.
It can help Your Highness
avoid false accusations.
Come on, come on.
Bring them in, bring them in.
Alright, alright, put them here.
Master!
-Father.
-Que.
-Mother.
How did you get here?
Yes, it was this...
Young hero.
He tied us up...
He escorted us all the way here.
He escorted us.
How did you manage that?
Anyway, I've brought them to you.
He also said
that Que is to marry Shen Du,
the Grand Commander Shen.
Grand Commander,
if you had such intentions,
you could have just told me.
Why bother with this surprise?
Yan Xing.
This matter,
you handle it.
[Prudence and Reverence]
Uncle, Aunt,
you've traveled all the way to Xiang'an,
I'm sure on the journey
you haven't had a chance to rest properly.
Why don't we take a break first?
We can discuss this matter later
and make plans then.
Sir and Madam,
please rest in the main hall.
[Prudence and Reverence]
Is this how you invite people?
You didn't specify how to bring them here.
Besides, they weren't cooperating.
Moreover,
this way is the safest for them to come.
Oh, right,
I found out something else
that you might be interested in.
Grand Commander Shen, please.
[Noble Aspiration] [Gentle and Humble]
Yun Que isn't here,
so let's get straight to the point.
Uncle, Aunt,
the reason we invited you to Xiang'an
is not about Yun Que's marriage.
Grand Commander Shen
has been sheltering Yun Que in his residence,
but has never had
any intention of marrying her.
Regarding the incident at Jinxiu Workshop years ago,
we hope that this time
you can tell us the truth.
What do you mean by this, Madam?
We don't understand.
Your journey to Xiang'an
hasn't been peaceful.
[Noble Aspiration] [Gentle and Humble]
I don't need to mention those assassins,
you must have heard about them.
At this point,
if you continue to hide the truth,
I'm afraid Grand Commander Shen
won't be able to protect you indefinitely.
That's true.
Indeed, my household has no obligation
to shelter irrelevant people.
Honey.
Since they are unwilling to say more,
then we
don't need to waste any more time.
I've heard that near Jinxiu Workshop,
[Noble Aspiration] [Gentle and Humble]
there have been restless spirits haunting us lately.
I am of a timid nature,
and I'd rather not invite more trouble.
Why don't we
pack up their belongings
and ask them to leave the Shen's Mansion under the cover of darkness?
Whether they live or die,
let it be their own fate.
Very well.
-Wait.
-Honey.
Que is innocent.
Uncle Yun,
we don't want
to see you in danger either.
But now,
someone is using the old Jinxiu Workshop case
to stir up trouble again.
Even if you conceal what you know,
do you really think the instigator
will protect you completely?
We've wronged Jinxiu Workshop.
We've wronged Boss Kong.
But
we were also forced by circumstances.
If we
had meddled in affairs that didn't concern us,
our entire Yun clan
wouldn't have survived.
When we checked the evidence back then,
we did find something unusual.
We thought about contacting Boss Kong immediately,
but that very night,
we were threatened.
They wanted us to keep quiet,
otherwise,
Yun Que would lose her life.
So we
have to abide by the agreement
and dare not speak up for Jinxiu Workshop.
Moreover, after all these years,
those who threatened us
have never stopped monitoring us.
If that's the case,
why did the evidence
end up in Yun Que's hands?
And she came alone,
safe and sound, to Xiang'an to seek justice.
It was that person
who told us to do this.
We couldn't understand
why they suddenly made such a request,
but
we had no choice but to comply.
We could only put on an act
to let Que know a thing or two.
With her personality,
she would definitely take those documents
and file a complaint.
The person who threatened you,
who exactly is it?
It's...
It's... it's Chen Huo'e.
-Que.
So,
you've known all along
that Uncle Kong's family was wrongly accused.
To protect yourselves,
you knew there was more to the story,
yet you disregarded Jinxiu Workshop
and the injustice done to so many people.
Que,
we had no choice.
Your mother and I
couldn't and didn't dare to risk your life
and the lives of the entire Yun family.
Father.
Mother.
Then how are we, the Yun family,
any different from accomplices?
It's your father and I who were cowards.
If there's any retribution,
let it fall upon us.
Que.
Grand Commander Shen and Mrs. Shen
also know you're not involved in this matter.
Only by staying in the Mrs. Shen
will you be safe.
I beg for your mercy, Grand Commander Shen.
Father,
Mother,
no matter what happens in the future,
I will face it together with you.
Que.
So,
is the truth more important,
or the safety of those around us
more important?
I didn't expect
it's Chen Huo'e again.
So she hasn't just recently come back to life,
but has been alive all along.
Over five years,
whatever Chen Huo'e
has been planning,
she must feel the time is ripe,
which is why she's using
all the evidence
to prove her resurrection.
What exactly is her purpose?
The act of deification through resurrection,
or even
a reinvestigation of the Jinxiu Workshop case.
The Jinxiu Workshop case back then
implicated the Princess Runing's mansion.
Now with a retrial,
using the moths to guide the people,
making people believe that Princess Ying
was the original instigator.
So it's...
To make the most favored member of the royal family,
Princess Ying,
be suspected,
distrusted,
or even incriminated.
If we want to investigate
the old case of Jinxiu Workshop,
it will inevitably involve
Princess Runing,
Princess Ying,
Prince Xian,
and even Prime Minister Zhang and Lai Luozhi,
the interactions between such high-ranking officials.
From the perspective of who benefits,
it is indeed difficult
not to suspect that the person behind it
is related to Princess Ying.
Chen Huo'e's deification efforts
are further guiding innocent people
to believe that
Princess Ying is the one
who needs to be punished.
What's wrong?
I now truly understand
proposing to reopen the old case
requires bearing such great
risks and pressure.
If Princess Ying is implicated,
it will involve
so many factions in the court.
Oh, right.
Pan Chi brought up another thing
on his return.
-He said...
-Grand Commander.
Princess Ying
is hosting a family banquet at her residence.
An invitation has been sent,
inviting you to attend.
I can't believe that at a time like this,
Princess Ying
still has the mood to host a family banquet.
I didn't expect it to come so soon.
Since you're curious,
why don't you accompany me?
[Wind and Rhyme]
It seems there are no
other female companions accompanying.
Then let's take this opportunity
to dispel the rumors
of our marital discord circulating in town.
That makes sense.
[Wind and Rhyme]
Then let's just
let them all see clearly.
Grand Commander.
Why did Princess Ying
take your advice
to host this family banquet?
Given her personality,
she would never allow rumors
to go unchecked.
She must be making a preemptive strike,
catching the turtle in the jar.
Are you so certain
that Chen Huo'e will take action?
Chen Huo'e wants to attract
more followers.
She needs to constantly create miracles,
and punishing the real culprits
of the Jinxiu Workshop case
is her best opportunity to showcase herself
and win people's hearts.
You've always stayed away from partisan disputes.
By attending this banquet today,
aren't you afraid that others might think
you've aligned yourself with Princess Ying?
Is the White Ghost, as people call me,
someone who cares about such things?
Honey, you're brilliantly clever.
If Chen Huo'e appears later,
what do you plan to do?
I'll play it by ear.
Princess Jia'an has arrived.
Greetings, Princess Jia'an.
May Princess Jia'an be safe and well.
Greetings, Mother.
May Mother be safe and well.
Come here quickly.
Today is a family banquet.
There's no need for excessive formalities, everyone.
Please be at ease.
Please, sit down.
Princess Jia'an is truly outstanding among people.
Her bearing is extraordinary,
[Princess Jia'an]
Just as the legends say,
her demeanor is impeccable.
Princess Jia'an is indeed worthy of being the daughter of Princess Ying.
It's an honor
to meet you today.
Jia'an has been frail since childhood.
She grew up in the suburban gardens of the capital.
With me, her mother,
we've spent more time apart than together.
Not long ago, she came of age.
She was then summoned back to the capital by the Empress Dowager.
Today's banquet
is for her,
to welcome her back.
I've heard that the Grand Empress Dowager
is personally arranging a marriage
for Princess Jia'an.
Your Highness will surely find her a dragon among men.
I actually hope
she could stay by my side
for a while longer.
Have you found anything?
A glance back with a smile outshines the stars.
She's truly at a wonderful age.
Look.
With all this singing and dancing,
it's truly a feast for the eyes and heart.
Be careful, joy can turn to sorrow.
Let's hope nothing goes wrong.
The moths.
I see them.
This...
Your Highness.
Guards!
Capture her alive!
Yes!
You've painstakingly prepared the show.
Are you going to leave without seeing it yourself?
So you've discovered it.
Such a trivial trick,
and you thought you could deceive me?
Since you can control the moths,
it naturally led me here
to find you, its master.
I'll give you credit for being clever.
However,
do you think you alone
can block my path?
It's enough.
You foolish creature,
then today
I'll leave you
with no way out.
If you don't align with me,
you'll be walking into a perilous situation
with no way out.
The unjust case of the Shen family back then,
does it have anything to do with you?
Your father
was nothing but an ant.
Even if he died, no one would care.
Why don't
you believe me
and beg me to resurrect him?
Smooth talk
and nonsense.
The person who framed your father
is right by your side.
Yet you mistake the culprit for your father,
aiding the tyrant in his cruelty.
Shen Du, oh Shen Du,
your father can't rest in peace.
You're asking for death.
Can people who come back from the dead
really bleed?
I've never believed that in this world
there could be people who come back from the dead.
Kill me,
and you'll lose another person who knows
about the unjust case of the Shen family from back then.
Xing, be careful!
Xing!
Shen Du.
Are you alright?
I know now
the key to Chen Huo'e's resurrection.
Let's go.
[Wind and Rhyme]
Your Highness,
Princess Jia'an has been frightened
and has taken a calming pill to rest.
Good.
Your Highness.
The assailant has been caught.
Your Grand Commander
indeed keeps his word.
Who sent you here?
No one.
Drag her out.
Beat her until she talks.
Yes.
You've all seen it today.
This so-called Fire Moth Sect,
this so-called boundless miracle,
is nothing but a group of people fooling the public,
deceiving the world,
mere charlatans.
From now on,
if anyone
uses Chen Huo'e's name again
to spread rumors,
this will be their fate.
Yes.
How could you be so careless?
It was...
It was Shen Du.
And Yan Xing.
They ruined my plans.
After today,
I'm afraid it will be difficult to have another chance
to get close to Princess Ying's Mansion.
I will do anything to eliminate enemies
for my master.
Forget it.
Bringing down Princess Ying
is not something that can be done overnight.
You fell into Shen Du's trap.
He wanted you to make a move.
As long as you can't fulfill the prophecy
and punish Princess Ying,
they will use it against you.
You'll lose the trust of your disciples and the people.
No.
I won't let Shen Du succeed.
Those who offend the Fire Moth
must all die.
Very good.
Then go and demonstrate
your miracle of rebirth again.
Don't move.
Next time we encounter Chen Huo'e,
we won't let her escape again.
You still want there to be a next time?
Now that she no longer has
the secret of immortality,
with your skills, capturing her
should be easy.
So,
it was Pan Chi who brought the news
that among the people
the Fire Moth Sect killed,
there was an old miracle doctor
who mentioned that he had treated someone
with transposed organs.
Based on just this one sentence,
you deduced that
Chen Huo'e's heart
is different from normal people's,
not on the left side.
I wasn't sure before,
but during our encounter,
I confirmed it.
Her heartbeat is on the right side.
Grand Commander.
Come in.
The guards watching the Fire Moth Sect disciples
have reported
some unusual activity.
What's the situation?
This morning, Chen Huo'e
appeared separately in the east,
west, south, and north of the city.
She claimed that the Fire Moth Sect has great supernatural powers,
not only can they bring people back from the dead,
but also create multiple incarnations.
In no time,
in the homes of Xiang'an City's residents,
they all started worshipping
various types of fire moths.
It seems the ambition of this Fire Moth Sect
is not limited to just within their sect.
[Cautiousness and Leniency]
Send out the notice.
Search the entire city for Chen Huo'e.
Yes, sir.
[Cautiousness and Leniency]
Keep an eye on the madam.
Don't let her wander around anymore.
Understood.
-Let me go!
Let go of me!
Take them all to the dungeon.
Yes, sir.
Grand Commander, bad news!
Grand Commander.
Madam is missing.
Missing?
Outside the Shen's Mansion,
those Fire Moth Sect thugs
are causing harm and chaos.
Saving people is the priority.
Open the gate.
The Grand Commander instructed before he left
that before his return,
the gates of the Shen's Mansion must not be opened under any circumstances.
If today, any common people
outside the Grand Commander's Mansion
meet with misfortune,
it would implicate the Grand Commander
in being unkind and unjust.
In the future, these gates
might truly never open again.
Open the door.
Save them.
[Shen's Mansion]
Madam and I went to rescue people.
We didn't expect to fall into their ambush.
In the blink of an eye,
Madam disappeared without a trace.
Let's go find her.
Let's go.
Moths to a flame.
Born at dawn, dead by dusk.
The moth has been resurrected.
The moth has shown its spirit.
Moths to a flame!
Born at dawn, dead by dusk!
Not entering the cycle of reincarnation.
Immortal reincarnation!
Moths to a flame!
Born at dawn, dead by dusk.
Moths to a flame.
Shen Du.
You can't kill me.
Give up.
A mere mirror image,
daring to impersonate immortality.
What a joke.
Shen Du.
Then today,
it's a fight to the death.
Xing.
Shen Du.
We can't let Chen Huo'e escape.
Shen Du!
Shen Du, wake up!
Jing Lin.
Shen Du.
Someone come here!
Someone come quickly!
Shen Du.
Jing Lin!
Grand Commander. Madam!
Shen Du.
Quickly take him back to the mansion.
Hurry!